Catholic Charities USA
The American Catholic Research Center and University Archives
- Series 7: Legislation Files, 1914(1928-1988)n.d.; (37 Boxes)
  - Subseries 7.2: Legislative Subject Files, 1949-1988; (30 Boxes)
    - Charitable Contributions - Data/Research, 1986, n.d. (Box 210, Folder 11)
    - Charitable Contributions - Survey of Public's Recollection of 1978 Charitable Donations, 1979 (Box 210, Folder 12)
    - Charitable Contributions - Verification, 1983-1984 (Box 210, Folder 13)
    - Charitable Disclosure, 1978-1979 (Box 210, Folder 14)
    - Charitable Procurement Act, 1984 (Box 210, Folder 15)
    - Charitable Solicitation, 1976 (Box 210, Folder 16)
    - Charitable Solicitation, 1977 (Box 210, Folder 17)
    - Charitable Solicitation, 1978-1984 (Box 210, Folder 18)
    - Charitably-Oriented Legislation, 1978-1979 (Box 210, Folder 19)
    - Child Custody, 1982 (Box 210, Folder 20)
    - Child and Family Services Act - S 626/HR 2966, 1974-1976 (Box 210, Folder 21)
    - Child Health Assurance Program, 1978-1979 (Box 210, Folder 22)
    - Child Health Assurance Program, 1979-1980 (Box 210, Folder 23)
    - Child Support, 1972-1976 (Box 210, Folder 24)
    - Child Welfare, 1978-1979 (Box 210, Folder 25)
    - Child Welfare - Impact of Child Welfare Act, 1985 (Box 210, Folder 26)
    - Child Welfare Block Grant, 1982-1986 (Box 210, Folder 27)
    - Church Audit, 1983-1984 (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Church Tax Exemptions, 1982 (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Church/State, 1973-1978 (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Church/State, 1979-1980 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Church/State (1), 1981 (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Church/State (2), 1981 (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Church/State, 1982-1983 (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - Church/State, 1984-1985 (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Church/State, 1986 (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Church/State, 1987-1988 (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Civil Rights Act, 1968, 1974-1975, 1978 (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Civil Rights Act, 1979-1980 (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Civil Rights Act, 1981-1983, 1986-1987, n.d. (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Civil Rights of Institutionalized Persons, 1978-1980 (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Collaboration Conference, 1979 (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - Commission on Federal Grants, 1975-1976 (Box 211, Folder 16)
    - Commission on Volunteerism, 1979 (Box 211, Folder 17)
    - Community Services Administration, 1977-1979 (Box 211, Folder 18)
    - Comprehensive Employment and Training Act, 1979-1980 (Box 211, Folder 19)
    - Conable Fisher Bill, 1978 (Box 211, Folder 20)
    - Confidentiality/Confessional Seal, 1973-1974, 1984 (Box 211, Folder 21)
    - Congress, 1980-1982 (Box 211, Folder 22)
    - Congressional Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 211, Folder 23)
    - Congressional Correspondence (1), 1980 (Box 211, Folder 24)
    - Congressional Correspondence (2), 1980 (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Correspondence, 1981 (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Congressional Correspondence - Corcoran, 1980-1981 (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1983 (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1984 (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Constitutional Convention, 1984-1985, n.d. (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Council on Accreditation - Board Meeting, June 1980 (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Council on Accreditation - Executive Committee, October 1980 (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Council on Accreditation - Board Meeting, December 1980 (Box 212, Folder 9)
    - Council on Accreditation, June 1981 (Box 212, Folder 10)
    - Daycare, 1975-1980 (Box 212, Folder 11)
    - Deans' Dinner - Boston, 1979 (Box 212, Folder 12)
    - Deans' Dinner - Louisville, 1980-1981 (Box 212, Folder 13)
    - Diocesan Attorneys, 1979, 1985 (Box 212, Folder 14)
    - Diocesan Profile, 1983-1984 (Box 212, Folder 15)
    - Divorce, 1972-1976 (Box 212, Folder 16)
    - Draft, 1973 (Box 212, Folder 17)
    - Durenberger hearing, 1974-September 1980 (Box 212, Folder 18)
    - Durenberger hearing, October-November 1980, n.d. (Box 212, Folder 19)
    - Dwan, Ralph Jr., 1977-1978 (Box 212, Folder 20)
    - Earnings Share, 1984 (Box 212, Folder 21)
    - Economist Proposal, 1973-1977 (Box 212, Folder 22)
    - Economic Equity Act, 1983 (Box 212, Folder 23)
    - Emergency Food and Shelter National Board Program, 1986 (Box 212, Folder 24)
    - Entitlement, 1981-1983 (Box 212, Folder 25)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1978, 1983-1984 (Box 212, Folder 26)
    - Establishment Clause, 1987 (Box 212, Folder 27)
    - Euthanasia, 1974-1977, 1983-1984 (Box 212, Folder 28)
    - Evangelization, 1979 (Box 212, Folder 29)
    - Fair Housing Amendments Act, 1979-1980 (Box 212, Folder 30)
    - Fairness Doctrine, 1981 (Box 212, Folder 31)
    - Family, 1965-1975 (Box 212, Folder 32)
    - Family (1), 1976 (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Family (2), 1976 (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - Family, 1977-1979 (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Family, 1980 (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Family, 1981-1982 (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Family, 1983-1986 (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Family Assistance Act, 1970 (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Families, Office of, 1979 (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Families, Office of, 1980 (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Families, Office of, 1981 (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Families, Office of, 1982-1983 (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - Family Planning, 1975-1978 (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - Families Proposed Project, 1981 (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - Family Violence, 1982-1986 (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - Farm Legislation, 1969 (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - Federal Emergency Management Agency, 1985-1986 (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - Flast v. Cohen (Supreme Court, no. 416), 1967 (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - Food Stamp Act - S 2547, 1969-1971 (Box 213, Folder 18)
    - Foster Care, 1976-1984 (Box 213, Folder 19)
    - Foster Care, 1984-1987, n.d. (Box 213, Folder 20)
    - Full Employment Act, 1978 (Box 213, Folder 21)
    - Full Employment - Humphrey Hawkins, 1976 (Box 213, Folder 22)
    - Foundations, 1981-1986 (Box 213, Folder 23)
    - Grants and Contracts Project, 1976-1983 (Box 213, Folder 24)
    - Grants and Contracts Project, 1983 (Box 213, Folder 25)
    - Grants and Contracts Project, 1984-1986, n.d. (Box 213, Folder 26)
    - Grants Interest Project, 1979 (Box 213, Folder 27)
    - Grants Interest Project, 1979-1980 (Box 213, Folder 28)
    - Grants Interest Project, n.d. (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Harvey, Fr. Thomas - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Harvey, Fr. Thomas - Correspondence (1), 1983 (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Harvey, Fr. Thomas - Correspondence (2), 1983 (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Harvey, Fr. Thomas - Correspondence (3), 1983 (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Harvey, Fr. Thomas - Correspondence (1), 1984 (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Harvey, Fr. Thomas - Correspondence (2), 1984 (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Harvey, Fr. Thomas - Correspondence (3), 1984 (Box 214, Folder 8)
    - Harvey, Fr. Thomas - Correspondence (4), 1984 (Box 214, Folder 9)
    - Harvey, Fr. Thomas - Correspondence, 1985, n.d. (Box 214, Folder 10)
    - Health Insurance, 1985-1986 (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Higgins, Msgr. George G., 1978-1981 (Box 214, Folder 12)
    - Homeless, 1984-1986 (Box 214, Folder 13)
    - Homeless Advocacy Materials, 1985 (Box 214, Folder 14)
    - Homeless, Ohio, 1984 (Box 214, Folder 15)
    - Homeless, Ohio, 1985 (Box 214, Folder 16)
    - Homeless, Ohio, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 17)
    - Homosexuality, 1973-1976 (Box 214, Folder 18)
    - Hospice Care, 1981-1982 (Box 214, Folder 19)
    - Housing, 1985 (Box 214, Folder 20)
    - Housing, 1986 (Box 214, Folder 21)
    - Housing - Advocate Contacts and Questionnaires, 1985 (Box 214, Folder 22)
    - Housing - Redlining/Disinvestment, 1974-1975 (Box 214, Folder 23)
    - Housing - Redlining/Disinvestment, 1975 (Box 214, Folder 24)
    - Housing - Redlining/Disinvestment, 1976, n.d. (Box 214, Folder 25)
    - Hunger, 1983-1984 (Box 214, Folder 26)
    - IRS (Internal Revenue Service), 1969, 1975-1978 (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - IRS (Internal Revenue Service), 1979-1984 (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Immigration, 1973-1977 (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Immigration, 1978-1982 (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Immigration, 1983, 1985 (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Immigration, 1986 (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Imputed Interest - Long-term Care, 1985 (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Independent Sector - Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 215, Folder 8)
    - Independent Sector - Government Relations Committee, June 1983 (Box 215, Folder 9)
    - Independent Sector - Government Relations Committee, December 1983 (Box 215, Folder 10)
    - Independent Sector - Government Relations Committee, March 1984 (Box 215, Folder 11)
    - Independent Sector - Government Relations Committee, June 1984 (Box 215, Folder 12)
    - Independent Sector - Government Relations Committee (1), September 1984 (Box 215, Folder 13)
    - Independent Sector - Government Relations Committee (2), September 1984 (Box 215, Folder 14)
    - Independent Sector - Government Relations Committee, December 1984 (Box 215, Folder 15)
    - Independent Sector - Lobbying Booklet, 1984 (Box 215, Folder 16)
    - Independent Sector - Lobbying Limitations, 1982-1983 (Box 215, Folder 17)
    - Independent Sector - OMB Circular A-122, 1983 (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - Independent Sector - Subcommittee on Government/IS Partnership, December 1983 (Box 215, Folder 19)
    - Independent Sector - Tax Issues Task Force, 1984 (Box 215, Folder 20)
    - Indians, 1973-1976 (Box 215, Folder 21)
    - Indians (1), 1977-1978 (Box 215, Folder 22)
    - Indians (2), 1977-1978 (Box 215, Folder 23)
    - Indians, 1978 (Box 215, Folder 24)
    - Indians (1), 1979 (Box 215, Folder 25)
    - Indians (2), 1979 (Box 215, Folder 26)
    - Indians, 1981 (Box 215, Folder 27)
    - Indians, 1982 (Box 215, Folder 28)
    - Indians, 1983 (Box 216, Folder 1)
    - Indians, 1984 (Box 216, Folder 2)
    - Indian Child Welfare Act, 1977 (Box 216, Folder 3)
    - Indian Child Welfare Act (1), 1978 (Box 216, Folder 4)
    - Indian Child Welfare Act (2), 1978 (Box 216, Folder 5)
    - Indian Child Welfare Act, 1979 (Box 216, Folder 6)
    - Indian Child Welfare Act, 1982, 1987, n.d. (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Indochinese Refugees, 1979 (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - In-kind Assistance, 1983 (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Integrated Auxiliary, 1976-1977 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Integrated Auxiliary, 1977 (Box 216, Folder 11)
    - Integrated Auxiliary, 1978-1983, n.d. (Box 216, Folder 12)
    - Integrated Auxiliary, 1984 (Box 216, Folder 13)
    - Insurance, 1973-1975 (Box 216, Folder 14)
    - J. P. Stevens, 1975-1981 (Box 216, Folder 15)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Amicus Briefs, 1987 (Box 216, Folder 16)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Amicus for Pat Geary (Title VI), 1978 (Box 216, Folder 17)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Amicus for Pat Geary (Title VI), 1987-1988 (Box 216, Folder 18)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Amicus for Pat Geary (Adolescent Family Act), 1981 (Box 216, Folder 19)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Amicus for Pat Geary (Title XX), 1984 (Box 216, Folder 20)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Amicus for Pat Geary, 1987-1988 (Box 216, Folder 21)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Analysis, 1988 (Box 216, Folder 22)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Appeal, 1987 (Box 216, Folder 23)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 1, 1983-1984 (Box 216, Folder 24)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 2, October 1983-August 1984 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 3, 1983-1984 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 4-1, 1981-1983, n.d. (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 4-2, 1984 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 4-3, 1984 (Box 217, Folder 5)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 5-1, 1984-1985 (Box 217, Folder 6)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 5-2, 1985-1986 (Box 217, Folder 7)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 6-1, 1983-1984 (Box 217, Folder 8)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 6-2, 1984-1985 (Box 217, Folder 9)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 7-1, 1987 (Box 217, Folder 10)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Case File 7-2, 1987 (Box 217, Folder 11)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler, 1987 (Box 217, Folder 12)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler, 1988 (Box 217, Folder 13)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 217, Folder 14)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Current, 1983-1987 (Box 217, Folder 15)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Decision, June 1988 (Box 217, Folder 16)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Field Surveys, 1987 (Box 217, Folder 17)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Supreme Court (1), 1987 (Box 217, Folder 18)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Supreme Court (2), 1987 (Box 217, Folder 19)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Supreme Court (1), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 20)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Supreme Court (2), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 21)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Supreme Court (3), 1988 (Box 217, Folder 22)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Supreme Court (4), 1988 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Kendrick v. Heckler - Supreme Court Ruling, 1988 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Land Reform, 1970-1973 (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Land Reform, 1973-1975 (Box 218, Folder 4)
    - Land Use, 1973-1975 (Box 218, Folder 5)
    - Legislative Issues, 1982-1986 (Box 218, Folder 6)
    - Life, 1967-1971 (Box 218, Folder 7)
    - Life, 1972 (Box 218, Folder 8)
    - Life, 1973, n.d. (Box 218, Folder 9)
    - Life (1), 1974 (Box 218, Folder 10)
    - Life (2), 1974 (Box 218, Folder 11)
    - Life, 1975 (Box 218, Folder 12)
    - Life, 1976 (Box 218, Folder 13)
    - Lobby Disclosure, 1983 (Box 218, Folder 14)
    - Lobby Restrictions, 1982 (Box 218, Folder 15)
    - Lobbying, 1983-1985 (Box 218, Folder 16)
    - Long Range Planning (1), 1984 (Box 218, Folder 17)
    - Long Range Planning (2), 1984 (Box 218, Folder 18)
    - Long Range Planning, 1985 (Box 218, Folder 19)
    - Long Range Planning Feedback, 1985, n.d. (Box 218, Folder 20)
    - Long Range Planning, 1986 (Box 218, Folder 21)
    - Long Range Planning, 1987 (Box 218, Folder 22)
    - Magazine Agencies, 1975-1977, 1983 (Box 218, Folder 23)
    - Mailing Houses, 1983 (Box 218, Folder 24)
    - Mandatory Retirement, 1977-1978 (Box 218, Folder 25)
    - Migrant Workers, 1973-1975 (Box 218, Folder 26)
    - Migrant Workers, 1976-1978 (Box 219, Folder 1)
    - Minimum Wage, 1971, 1973-1976, 1980 (Box 219, Folder 2)
    - Minimum Wage, 1981, 1983 (Box 219, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box 219, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Legislation, 1975 (Box 219, Folder 5)
    - Model State Adoption Act, 1978-1980 (Box 219, Folder 6)
    - Model State Adoption Act, 1980 (Box 219, Folder 7)
    - Canon Joseph Moerman, 1975, 1979-1981 (Box 219, Folder 8)
    - NCCC - Ad Hoc Publications Committee Meeting, March 1983 (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - NCCC - Alternative Services Questionnaire, 1982 (Box 219, Folder 10)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Complaints, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 11)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Complaints, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 12)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Entertainment, 1978-1979 (Box 219, Folder 13)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Hotel, 1978-1979 (Box 219, Folder 14)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Letterhead, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 15)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Liturgy, 1978-1979 (Box 219, Folder 16)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Post Event Thank You Letters, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 17)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Program Production and Printing, 1978-1979 (Box 219, Folder 18)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Prospect List, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 19)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Publicity, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 20)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Special Event Evaluation, 1979 (Box 219, Folder 21)
    - NCCC - Anniversary - Special Event Information, 1978-1979 (Box 219, Folder 22)
    - NCCC - Annual Meeting, 1976 (Box 219, Folder 23)
    - NCCC - Annual Survey, 1981-1982 (Box 219, Folder 24)
    - NCCC - Annual Survey (1), 1983 (Box 219, Folder 25)
    - NCCC - Annual Survey (2), 1983 (Box 219, Folder 26)
    - NCCC - Annual Survey, 1984 (Box 219, Folder 27)
    - NCCC - Board of Counselors, 1983 (Box 219, Folder 28)
    - NCCC - Board Meeting, 1976-1979 (Box 219, Folder 29)
    - NCCC - Bylaws, n.d. (Box 219, Folder 30)
    - NCCC - Charities USA, 1982-1983 (Box 219, Folder 31)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice (1), 1973 (Box 219, Folder 32)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice (2), 1973 (Box 219, Folder 33)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice (1), 1974 (Box 219, Folder 34)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice (2), 1974 (Box 219, Folder 35)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice (3), 1974 (Box 219, Folder 36)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice, 1974, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice, 1975-1977 (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice, 1978-1979 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice (1), 1980 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice (2), 1980 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice, 1981 (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - NCCC - Committee on Legislation for Social Justice, n.d. (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - NCCC - Correspondence, 1968, 1970 (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - NCCC - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - NCCC - Correspondence, 1972 (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - NCCC - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 220, Folder 11)
    - NCCC - Government Relations/Transparencies, 1983-1985 (Box 220, Folder 12)
    - NCCC - Income Maintenance, 1969-1970, 1974 (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - NCCC - Land Use Task Force, 1979-1980 (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - NCCC - Legislative Briefings, 1976 (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - NCCC - Legislative Briefings, 1981 (Box 220, Folder 16)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting (Boston), 1974 (Box 220, Folder 17)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting (Chicago), 1974 (Box 220, Folder 18)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting (Mid-year), 1974-1975 (Box 220, Folder 19)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee, 1975 (Box 220, Folder 20)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting, April 7-8, 1975 (Box 220, Folder 21)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting, October 17-18, 1975 (Box 220, Folder 22)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee, 1976 (Box 220, Folder 23)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting (Chicago), 1976 (Box 220, Folder 24)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting (Denver), 1976 (Box 220, Folder 25)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1976 (Box 220, Folder 26)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting, January 1976 (Box 220, Folder 27)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting (1), December 1977 (Box 220, Folder 28)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting (2), December 1977 (Box 220, Folder 29)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee - Tax Reform (Draft Policy), 1977 (Box 220, Folder 30)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting, October 1978 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Mandate, 1978-1979 (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Role, 1978-1979 (Box 221, Folder 3)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1979 (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee, April 1980 (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee (1), November 1980 (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee (2), November 1980 (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting, May 1981 (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee (1), November 1981 (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee (2), November 1981 (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee (3), November 1981 (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee, 1982 (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting, September 1982 (Box 221, Folder 15)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee Meeting, November 1982 (Box 221, Folder 16)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee (1), 1983 (Box 221, Folder 17)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee (2), 1983 (Box 221, Folder 18)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee - Materials for Memo, 1975, n.d. (Box 221, Folder 19)
    - NCCC - Legislative Committee - Survey on Secondary Migration, 1984 (Box 221, Folder 20)
    - NCCC - Legislative Goals, 1973-1974 (Box 221, Folder 21)
    - NCCC - Legislative Program, 93rd Congress, 1973-1975 (Box 221, Folder 22)
    - NCCC - Legislative Program, 94th Congress, 1975-1976 (Box 221, Folder 23)
    - NCCC - Legislative Program, 95th and 96th Congress (1), 1976-1981 (Box 221, Folder 24)
    - NCCC - Legislative Program, 95th and 96th Congress (2), 1976-1981 (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - NCCC - Legislative Program, 95th and 96th Congress (3), 1976-1981 (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - NCCC - Legislative Program, 97th Congress, 1981-1983 (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - NCCC - Legislative Program, 98th Congress (1), 1983-1985 (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - NCCC - Legislative Program, 98th Congress (2), 1983-1985 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - NCCC - Legislative Program, 99th Congress, 1985 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - NCCC - Legislative Seminar - Agenda, 1976-1979 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - NCCC - Legislative Seminar - Financial, 1979 (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - NCCC - Legislative Seminar - Handouts, 1979 (Box 222, Folder 9)
    - NCCC - Legislative Seminar - Logistics, 1979 (Box 222, Folder 10)
    - NCCC - Legislative Seminar - Needs Assessment, 1979 (Box 222, Folder 11)
    - NCCC - Legislative Training, 1981 (Box 222, Folder 12)
    - NCCC - Legislative Workshop - Annual Meeting, 1973 (Box 222, Folder 13)
    - NCCC - Legislative Workshop - Boston, 1973-1974 (Box 222, Folder 14)
    - NCCC - Love Canal, 1980-19781 (Box 222, Folder 15)
    - NCCC - Mailing, 1974, 1976, 1984-1985 (Box 222, Folder 16)
    - NCCC - Miscellaneous, 1979 (Box 222, Folder 17)
    - NCCC - National Health Insurance Task Force, 1974, 1978-1980 (Box 222, Folder 18)
    - NCCC - National Health Insurance Task Force (1), 1980 (Box 222, Folder 19)
    - NCCC - National Health Insurance Task Force (2), 1980 (Box 222, Folder 20)
    - NCCC - National Health Insurance Task Force, 1981-1982 (Box 222, Folder 21)
    - NCCC - Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1975 (Box 222, Folder 22)
    - NCCC - Newspaper Clippings, 1976 (Box 222, Folder 23)
    - NCCC - Newspaper Clippings, 1977-1981 (Box 222, Folder 24)
    - NCCC - Newspaper Clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 222, Folder 25)
    - NCCC - Nominations Committee, 1984-1985 (Box 222, Folder 26)
    - NCCC - Nominations Committee, 1985, n.d. (Box 222, Folder 27)
    - NCCC - Nominations Committee, 1986 (Box 222, Folder 28)
    - NCCC - Nominations Committee, 1987 (Box 222, Folder 29)
    - NCCC - Office Procedures, 1984 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - NCCC - Personnel Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - NCCC - Personnel Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - NCCC - Photographs (Colorfax), 1984-1985 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - NCCC - Publications Department Reports, 1983 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - NCCC - Resolutions, 1982 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - NCCC - Response to Economic Summit, 1974-1975 (Box 223, Folder 7)
    - NCCC - Social Action, 1984 (Box 223, Folder 8)
    - NCCC - Social Security/Retirement, 1979-1981 (Box 223, Folder 9)
    - NCCC - Sponsoring Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 223, Folder 10)
    - NCCC - Tax Reform, 1977 (Box 223, Folder 11)
    - National Assembly, 1983-1985 (Box 223, Folder 12)
    - National Assembly Communications Group, 1980-1982 (Box 223, Folder 13)
    - National Catholic Conference for Interracial Justice, 1985-1986 (Box 223, Folder 14)
    - National Conference of Catholic Bishops (NCCB), 1983 (Box 223, Folder 15)
    - National Commission for the Protection of Human Subjects of Biomedical and Behavioral Research, 1974-1976 (Box 223, Folder 16)